http://www.codehost.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Codehost, Inc. ("Codehost, Inc.") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect from you, either online or offline, and how that information will be used. Please read this Privacy Statement carefully. Should you have any questions, please refer to the end of the Statement for information on how to contact us.
The Information We Collect
Personal Information
You may visit our web site and not provide us with any information that can identify you. But if you decide to download a driver or contact Codehost, Inc. to request information or support, complete a survey, enter a contest or sweepstakes, submit a rebate, inquire about products you may already license, request samples of certain products or provide a product review or other feedback, we may collect information such as your name, e-mail or postal address, phone number and credit card information ("Personal Information").
Non-Personal Information
We may also collect non-personal information from various sources. This information, also known as anonymous or aggregate data, is data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual:
Information collected automatically. When you visit our web site, we collect certain information automatically. This information includes the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet, information about your browser type and language, the date and time you are accessing our web site, and the referring web site address. It may also include technical data about the Codehost products you are using.
Use of cookies and other technologies. We may collect information about your use of our web site through the following means:
Cookies. We don’t engage in collecting information or tapping information through the use of cookies.
Other Technologies. We may use analytics software to collect general information on our web traffic and related use items, including among others, browsers used, searches used, time spent on site, etc...
How We Use Information
In General. We may use the information we collect about you to respond to your requests for information; to deliver the products and services you have requested; to manage your account and provide you with customer support; to provide you with information about other products and promotions that may be of interest to you; to obtain feedback on our products and services; to perform research and analysis about usage and potential interest in our products, services, or content; to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our web site; to enforce our Terms and Conditions and to perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
With Whom We Share Your Information
Our customers are a critical component of our business and we are not in the business of selling or renting your personal information to third-parties. We may share information with manufacturers of hardware that we supported. Such as manufacturers that sponsor the free drivers available from Codehost for their hardware devices. If you provide information to download a driver for a specific device, we may share such information with the manufacturer of that device.
Finally, we also may share your personal information:
In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our web site Terms and Conditions or other agreements or policies.
In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
Opt-out Option
Anyone may opt out of registering or providing information or have their information deleted from our system at any time by emailing us at info@codehost.com, with the subject “Opt-out”. This option does not supersede or replace your contract on licensed software, whether the software is downloaded from our site or obtained through third parties, including all the obligations set forth in such contract.
Third-Party Web Sites and Interest-Based Marketing Links
There are a number of places on our web site where you may click on a link to access other web sites that do not operate under this Privacy Statement. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a third-party logo on our web site, you may be taken to a web site that we do not control. These third-party web sites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party web sites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the web page you are visiting.
Right to Change Internet Privacy Statement
This Statement was last updated effective November 8, 2011. Codehost, Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time. If we make any material changes to this Statement, we will notify you by posting the changes on our web site. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the web site. Your continued use of our web site following the postings of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
How To Contact Us
Should you have questions or concerns about this Statement, please email your inquiry to Codehost, Inc. – subject: Customer Privacy to info@codehost.com
Download BrightQ™ Pro for Canon
Select Version...
— US & Canada Users —>>
Linux
Solaris
HP-UX
AIX
FreeBSD
— Outside US & Canada —>>
Canon International (BrightQ™ SE only)
Canon Latin America
— Legacy Versions —>>
BrightQ™ v2.4.4 for IRIX
BrightQ™ v2.4.4 for SCO
Download
Download BrightQ™ for other brands
Select Brand...
Ricoh
Sharp
Kyocera
Savin
Lanier
Canon (outside Americas)
Download
NOTICE: By downloading any files or documents found on this page, you are agreeing to this disclaimer.
Read our Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
NOTICE TO USER: THIS IS A CONTRACT.
BY USING THIS SITE YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE TERMS OF USE USE AGREEMENT BELOW. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of the .TERMS OF USE. Agreement, do not download ANY ITEMS FROM THIS SITE.
BY DOWNLOADING ANY DOCUMENT OR SOFTWARE FROM THIS WEB SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE END USER AGREEMENT PROVIDED WITH THE SOFTWARE THAT YOU DOWNLOAD FROM THIS SITE.
CANON AND CODEHOST MAKE NO GUARANTEES OF ANY KIND WITH REGARD TO ANY PROGRAMS, FILES, DRIVERS OR ANY OTHER MATERIALS CONTAINED ON OR DOWNLOADED FROM THIS, OR ANY OTHER, CODEHOST SOFTWARE SITE. ALL SUCH PROGRAMS, FILES, DRIVERS AND OTHER MATERIALS ARE SUPPLIED “AS IS.” CANON AND CODEHOST DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
CANON AND CODEHOST SHALL NOT BE HELD LIABLE FOR ERRORS CONTAINED HEREIN, OR FOR LOST PROFITS, LOST OPPORTUNITIES, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES INCURRED AS A RESULT OF ACTING ON INFORMATION, OR THE OPERATION OF ANY SOFTWARE, INCLUDED IN THIS SOFTWARE SITE.
By using this web site, you agree to these terms and conditions. Codehost reserves all rights to change these terms and conditions, and the products, services, prices, and programs mentioned in this web site at any time, at its sole discretion, without notice. Codehost reserves the right to seek all remedies available by law and in equity for any violation of these terms and conditions.
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Codehost, Inc. (“Codehost”) makes available information and products on this web site, subject to these terms and conditions, as follows:
The software, source code, and accompanying documentation available to download from this web site are copyrighted by Codehost, various other companies and individuals. Use of the software is governed by the terms of the end user license agreement, which accompanies such software. If no license accompanies the download, the terms of the license, which accompanied the original product being updated, will govern.
Except as otherwise indicated on this web site, you may view, print, copy, and distribute documents found on this web site subject to the following terms and conditions:
The document may be used solely for informational, personal, non-commercial purposes;
Any copy of the document or portion thereof must include all copyright and proprietary notices in the same form and manner as on the original;
The document may not be modified in any way; And
Codehost reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately upon notice from Codehost.
Documents specified above do not include the layout or design of this website. Elements of this web site are protected by trade dress or other laws and may not be imitated or reproduced in whole or in part.
Documents specified above do not include logos, graphics, sounds or images on this web site, which may be reproduced or distributed only when expressly permitted by Codehost.
EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE IN AN AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND CODEHOST, ALL INFORMATION AND SOFTWARE ON THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.
CODEHOST ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE INFORMATION OR SOFTWARE OR OTHER DOCUMENTS WHICH ARE REFERENCED BY OR LINKED TO THIS WEB SITE. IN NO EVENT SHALL CODEHOST BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM: (1) RELIANCE ON THE MATERIALS PRESENTED, (2) COSTS OF REPLACEMENT GOODS, (3) LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, (4) DELAYS OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTIONS, (5) AND ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF INFORMATION) WHETHER OR NOT CODEHOST HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. THIS WEB SITE COULD INCLUDE TECHNICAL OR OTHER INACCURACIES. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY MADE TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. HOWEVER, CODEHOST MAKES NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE MATERIALS ON THIS SITE.
Codehost does not want to receive confidential or proprietary information through its web site. Any information sent to Codehost will be deemed NOT CONFIDENTIAL. You grant Codehost an unrestricted, irrevocable license to display, use, modify, perform, reproduce, transmit, and distribute any information you send Codehost, for any and all commercial and non-commercial
purposes.
You also agree that Codehost is free to use any ideas, concepts, or techniques that you send Codehost for any purpose, including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing products that incorporate such ideas, concepts, or techniques.
Codehost permits anyone to link to Codehost’s web site subject to the linkers’ compliance with the following terms and conditions. A web site that links to Codehost’s web site:
May link to, but not replicate, content contained in Codehost’s web site; Must not create a border environment, frame, or browser around content contained in Codehost’s web site; Must not present misleading or false information about Codehost’s services or products; Must not misrepresent Codehost’s relationship with the linker; Must not imply that Codehost is endorsing or sponsoring the linker or the linkers’ services or products; Must not use Codehost’s logos or trade dress without prior written permission from Codehost; Must not contain content that could be construed as obscene, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, or inappropriate for all ages; Must not contain materials that would violate any laws; Must agree that the link may be removed at any time upon Codehost’s request pursuant to Codehost’s reserved rights to rescind its consent to
allow the link.
Codehost’s web site provides links to third-party web sites, which are not under the control of Codehost. Codehost makes no representations about third-party web sites. When you access a non-Codehost web site, you do so at your own risk. Codehost is not responsible for the reliability of any data, opinions, advice, or statements made on third-party web sites. Codehost provides these links merely as a convenience. The inclusion of such links does not imply that Codehost endorses, recommends, or accepts any responsibility for the content of such sites.
The Codehost web site contains mention of third-party products and services for informational purposes. Codehost makes no recommendations or endorsements about third-party products and services. References to third-party services and products are provided by Codehost “as is”, without warranty of any kind, either express or implied.
You agree that all matters relating to your access to, or use of, this web site shall be governed by the laws of the state of California. Codehost makes no representation that information on this web site are appropriate or available for use in all countries, and prohibits accessing materials from territories where contents are illegal. Those who access this web site do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with all applicable laws.
Software available on the Codehost web site is subject to United States export controls. No software from this web site may be downloaded or otherwise exported or re-exported: (1) into (or to a national or resident of) Cuba, Iraq, Libya, Sudan, North Korea, Iran, or any other country to
which the United States has embargoed goods; or (2) to anyone on the United States Treasury Department’s list of Specially Designated Nationals or the United States Commerce Department’s Table of Denial and Prohibition Orders.
By downloading or using software from this web site, you are agreeing to the foregoing and all applicable export control laws. You are also warranting that you are not under the control of, located in, or a resident or national of any such country or on any such list. The information on export laws provided herein is not necessarily complete. For more information on export laws, please refer to 15 C.F.R. Â§736, 738, 744, 746, or telephone the United States Commerce Department, Bureau of Export Administration at (202) 482-2440, or (202) 482-4811.
Mininum Linux Distributions
RedHat EL 4
CentOS 4
Fedora 7
Ubuntu 9.10
SuSE / OpenSuSE 7.3
Debian 3.0
Slackware 10
TurboLinux 10.0
Minimum UNIX Versions
Solaris 10
HP-UX 11i
FreeBSD 8.2
IBM AIX 4.3
The BrightQ™ printing suite becomes more powerful and user-friendly with Codehost's latest release, BrightQ Pro 2.5.
BrightQ™ Pro, considered the de-facto UNIX and Linux printing standard for the multi-function copier market, includes a number of new features and product enhancements. BrightQ™ has been adopted by many industry-leading printing companies.
